<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Product Management on Product Solo: Product Management for Everyone.</title>
    <link>https://productsolo.github.io/tags/product-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Product Management on Product Solo: Product Management for Everyone.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2024, Product Solo.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:06:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://productsolo.github.io/tags/product-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prioritaskan Produkmu Dengan Value vs Effort Framework</title>
      <link>https://productsolo.github.io/blog/prioritaskan-produkmu-dengan-value-vs-effort-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:06:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://productsolo.github.io/blog/prioritaskan-produkmu-dengan-value-vs-effort-framework/</guid>
      <description>oleh Thariq Luqmana
Jangan Bikin Produkmu Stuck! Prioritaskan dengan Value vs Effort framework! Mengelola produk bisa menjadi perjalanan yang menantang dan penuh dengan keputusan penting. Salah satu tantangan terbesar yang sering dihadapi Product Manager adalah menentukan prioritas fitur dan inisiatif. Dengan begitu banyak ide brilian yang muncul, memilih mana yang harus dikerjakan terlebih dahulu bisa menjadi tugas yang membingungkan. Di sinilah Metode Value vs Effort masuk sebagai penyelamat! Metode ini adalah pendekatan sederhana namun efektif untuk membantu Product Manager menentukan prioritas dan memastikan bahwa produk yang dikembangkan memberikan dampak maksimal dengan usaha minimal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO Skill Untuk Product Manager</title>
      <link>https://productsolo.github.io/blog/seo-skill-untuk-product-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 12:14:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://productsolo.github.io/blog/seo-skill-untuk-product-manager/</guid>
      <description>oleh Mochammad Ihza Rizky Karim
Awalan Hai pembaca Product Solo, pada artikel kali ini akan dibahasa mengenai SEO Skill Untuk Product Manager. Seperti yang diketahui, bahwa product manager merupaan pekerjaan yang saat ini banyak didambakan oleh freshgraduate untuk menjadi pekerjaannya, banyak dari mereka juga belajar mengenai manajemen produk melalui bootcamp, youtube dan sebagainya. Namun, seiring perkembangan teknologi, product manager diharuskan tau banyak skill seperti AI, Data Analisis, Design, API dan tak terkecuali Search Engine Optimization (SEO).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways to be a Product Manager</title>
      <link>https://productsolo.github.io/blog/3-ways-to-be-a-product-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:18:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://productsolo.github.io/blog/3-ways-to-be-a-product-manager/</guid>
      <description>by Mochammad Ihza Rizky Karim
Intro Are you having a hard time getting a job as a product manager?
Do you feel lacking in terms of portfolio and experience in the field of product management?
Currently, especially in Indonesia, when there are jobs as product managers from junior to senior level, and even internships, it is almost certain that there are more than 100 applicants with only a few vacancies opened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacher to Product Manager</title>
      <link>https://productsolo.github.io/blog/teacher-to-product-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 15:14:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://productsolo.github.io/blog/teacher-to-product-manager/</guid>
      <description>Intro Today, finding a job is so challenging for many people, ranging from employees who have been laid off and freshgraduates from campuses. The job that until this article was made, there are still many enthusiasts are product managers, from junior to senior level and up to executive level. Many people compete to become product managers from starting with a software engineer background to some from a teacher background.
But, indeed, product management is a very possible field of work from any background, depending on what industry will be worked on as a product manager.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
